They have been around for a while, I do not know how long but kind of a year I have for myself or a little more.
They have previously only offered fund trading, but now they have launched stock trading as well.
They then offer a 25% discount on all funds and also interest on ISK.
So I usually say it, if you start saving, start at Avanza, up to 50,000.
If you want to buy more shares after that, then go to Nordnet, then you have up to 80,000 but only within 6 months.
So there you have a time limit.
At Levler there is then no time limit, or there is no amount limit I mean, but the time limit is until March and since 2025 then.
Then it will start to cost commission.
But the commission at Levler will be cheaper than at Avanza.
I put graphics here, compare, here you can see the price of Levler, here you can see the price of Avanza and Nordnet.
First and foremost then, what can you shop at Levler?
Well, you can buy shares on the Swedish stock exchange, that is, the Stockholm Stock Exchange, not, for example, Spotlight.